<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Security on Cole Cornford</title>
    <link>https://colecornford.com/tags/web-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Security on Cole Cornford</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://colecornford.com/tags/web-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SameSite Cookies! Coming to break your website Feb2020.</title>
      <link>https://colecornford.com/2019-oct-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colecornford.com/2019-oct-2/</guid>
      <description>Hey friends!
Today i wanted to talk about the SameSite cookie attribute, and how the browser flip from Off to On by default is well. .. kind of going to screw up the internet internet in Australia in Feb 2020.
What is SameSite SameSite is a cookie security attribute that was introduced to address cross-site request forgery. A cookie is a piece of data sent from a website and stored in the web browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subresource Integrity - Gecko Deep Dive</title>
      <link>https://colecornford.com/2019-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colecornford.com/2019-may/</guid>
      <description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing code reviews of applications and have been recommending they take advantage of the security benefits that Subresource Integrity provides. This article will go into some detail about what it is and by analysing the Gecko source code some subtle nuances we can learn about it.
What and why? I think an example would help illustrate the problem. When you navigate to a webpage, you initially perform a TCP Handshake on whichever Origin you attempt to navigate to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy as C S P!</title>
      <link>https://colecornford.com/2019-apr-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colecornford.com/2019-apr-2/</guid>
      <description>One of my avid readers the other day sent me a screenshot of my website run through an automated tool.
Well then, I suck and I guess I&amp;rsquo;ll have to close up my AppSec blog now!
..
But really, I think it&amp;rsquo;s good to talk about what&amp;rsquo;s going on here.
D Grade A cool dude by the name of Scott Helme released securityheaders.com which will submit a HTTP request to the domain you specified, receive a response, and then analyse the headers that were in the response.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
