<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cole Cornford</title>
    <link>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cole Cornford</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging Platform Choices</title>
      <link>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/post/2015-01-04-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/post/2015-01-04-first-post/</guid>
      <description>I was laying on my lounge for New Years Eve 2018 (boring i know hey?).
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t that bad, I was watching my favourite MTG Streamer playing Sorin&amp;rsquo;s Vengeance + Twincast, a beautiful&amp;hellip; if not infuriating combination of magic cards.
I had realised I had gone through 2018 without terribly many technical achievements in work and life. Sure, I had learned an amazing amount from my wonderful colleagues like Farooq, Nina, and Stefano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/resources/</guid>
      <description>Resources I read and research a lot, so I thought i would curate all the things I find to help others get to the useful content.
I&amp;rsquo;ll also do shorthand reviews here for books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact me</title>
      <link>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/contact/</guid>
      <description>I regularly attend developer and security conferences and spend a bunch of time in Sydney cafes and bars, so feel free to come bug me there.
This year I&amp;rsquo;m looking to attend or speak at:
 BSides Canberra Bsides Brisbane Bsides Sydney NDC Security Gold Coast Kiwicon  You can also reach me on LinkedIn or at Twitter, or just send me an email.
Peace!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/projects/</guid>
      <description>This year I&amp;rsquo;m looking at either starting, continuing, or contributing to the below projects. Some are ideas I&amp;rsquo;ve kicked around with a few mates, others there&amp;rsquo;s definitely an industry gap I&amp;rsquo;d like to fill, and then others are just experimenting with something cool.
No real priorities, so please let me know what you&amp;rsquo;re interested in!
I&amp;rsquo;m also available for consulting, so feel free to email me if you&amp;rsquo;d like to work together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Here!</title>
      <link>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thirsty-brown-e272aa.netlify.com/page/start/</guid>
      <description>Who am I? Welcome friends! I&amp;rsquo;m Cole, an AppSec professional who can&amp;rsquo;t stop speaking when I get put on a stage. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got an interest in InfoSec and personal development then I hope you find the things I write about the to be valuable to you!
What&amp;rsquo;s this about? I&amp;rsquo;ve met a lot of damn smart people in the InfoSec space. Pen-testers, Architects, Engineers, you name it! Despite all of these talented people working hard to solve REAL problems, the same issues continue to crop up:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>