<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General Security on Cole Cornford</title>
    <link>https://colecornford.com/tags/general-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General Security on Cole Cornford</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://colecornford.com/tags/general-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CSP Adoption in Australia</title>
      <link>https://colecornford.com/2021-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colecornford.com/2021-may/</guid>
      <description>Hi friends!
Welcome back to my series of security blog posts. I hope to write these on a weekly basis. If you have any feedback, feel free to message me on LinkedIn!
A B C S P Originally, the Content Security Policy was developed to counter an influx of Cross-Site Scripting attacks. Fundamentally, if you knew what content was being placed in your website, you should be able to specify as policy specifically what you trust and from where.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Quality vs Code Security.</title>
      <link>https://colecornford.com/2020-jan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colecornford.com/2020-jan/</guid>
      <description>Today, I was reviewing some source code for security weaknesses. I stumbled across code that made me chuckle. Something along these lines.
public String XOR(String method, String input, String key) { if (method == &amp;quot;Encrypt&amp;quot;) { return XOR_Encrypt(input, key); } else if (method == &amp;quot;Decrypt&amp;quot;) { return XOR_Decrypt(input, key); } else { return input; } }  As software engineers, we have all contributed in our own way to the legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AppSec 101 - Where Do I Begin?</title>
      <link>https://colecornford.com/2019-apr-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colecornford.com/2019-apr-1/</guid>
      <description>I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write a series of blog posts covering the core aspects of Application Security, and I&amp;rsquo;m not talking about vulnerabilities. I&amp;rsquo;m going to start with well.. the start!
Setting the Stage Generally, when organisations are first starting to think about or begin to implement an AppSec strategy, the following scenario happens in one way or another.
Mr CIO walks into work, sits down with his double shot espresso from his local barista and writes up the following email to the organisations CISO.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
